<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Serendephia</title><link>http://www.serendeiphia.net/tags/serendephia/</link><description>Recent content on Serendephia</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.serendeiphia.net/tags/serendephia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creating art</title><link>http://www.serendeiphia.net/posts/creating/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.serendeiphia.net/posts/creating/</guid><description>Creating art, finding healing…The discovery of creating through art heals and transforms you. Art that does not heal is not art.
The perception of art moves us, drives us, and awakens desire, emotion, admiration, and longing. It mobilizes our thinking and feeling, stimulates reflection, which is the path to wisdom, and elevated emotions, which are the path to generosity and inspiration.
The emotions captured from art can even break our perceptual and mental schemes, open up possibilities, break false impossibilities, and invite us to travel through the unknown to reach what we long for within a journey towards ourselves.</description></item><item><title>The magic of Serendiphia…</title><link>http://www.serendeiphia.net/posts/magic/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.serendeiphia.net/posts/magic/</guid><description>The magic of Serendiphia… Serendiphia comes from the word Serendipity whose meaning catches us with that touch of mystery and surprise. It is charged with positive energy and stealthily emerges in our lives to show us something that we did not see but that we appreciate for the well-being and fascination that it transmits to us.
Undoubtedly, serendipities are gifts that come at the right time so as not to leave us indifferent.</description></item><item><title>What is Serendephia?</title><link>http://www.serendeiphia.net/posts/seredenphia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.serendeiphia.net/posts/seredenphia/</guid><description>Do you know what a serendipity is? Surely more than once something has come into your life that you did not expect but that has been a great discovery for you. It may even be a person who, without knowing how or when, was able to unexpectedly turn your life around.
The point is that it arrived without warning but it was so fascinating that you don&amp;rsquo;t even believe it could have happened.</description></item></channel></rss>